Mayer, Harold and Lynne "The Inheritance" Records 6389
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Harold and Lynne Mayer "The Inheritance" Records
1961-2008
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Mayer, Harold
Mayer, Lynne
Mayer and Sklar Productions
Harold Mayer Productions
6389
1 cubic feet
1 linear ft.
Reports, pamphlets, correspondence, agreements, publications.
8596606
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Related Materials
Related Collections: 6118 AV: Kheel Center AV Collection 6389 AV: Harold and Lynne Mayer "The Inheritance" Audio-Visual Materials 6389 P: Harold and Lynne Mayer "The Inheritance" Photographs [Deaccessioned]
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives 227 Ives Hall Tower Road Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183 kheelref@cornell.edu https://catherwood.library.cornell.edu/kheel/
Compiled by:
Kheel Staff, August 05, 2014
EAD encoding:
Kheel Staff, May 08, 2015
Mayer, Harold; Mayer, Lynne; Mayer and Sklar Productions; Harold Mayer Productions
8596606
- Agreement with George Kleinsinger, 1964-1965 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- Awards and Correspondences from Festivals, 1964-2008 (Box 1, Folder 2)
- Book, 1964 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Canadian Broadcasting Corporation Agreement, 1965-1974 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Correspondence, General, 1963-1979 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- Correspondence with Millard Lampell, 1961-1964 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- Descriptions and Synopses (Box 1, Folder 7)
- Legal, 1962-1982 (Box 1, Folder 8)
- Notices of Showings, 1964 (Box 1, Folder 9)
- Music, 1963-1984 (Box 1, Folder 10)
- Publicity (Box 1, Folder 11)
- Sales and Repairs of Film, 1985-1986 (Box 1, Folder 12)
- Sales of Videotapes, 1985-1990 (Box 1, Folder 13)
- Sales of Videotapes, 1991-1994 (Box 1, Folder 14)
- Sales of Videotapes, 1995-2001 (Box 1, Folder 15)
- Scripts (Box 1, Folder 16)
- Still Log (Box 1, Folder 17)
- Stills Used, 1962-1964 (Box 1, Folder 18)
- Stock Footage Contracts, 1963-1964 (Box 1, Folder 19)
- Theatre Agreement, 1964 (Box 1, Folder 20)
- Title Copy (Box 1, Folder 21)